[{"answer": " Hanna, please come in.  Its a pleasure to meet you.  Im Ally Smith", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you too", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hanna, please come in.  Its a pleasure to meet you.  Im Ally Smith", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " How can I help you today", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Thank you.  Its nice to meet you too", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": "Im going to apply to graduate school at some universities in the U.S., and I", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " How can I help you today", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " OK.  What kind of help did you need?  Have you written them already", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Im going to apply to graduate school at some universities in the U.S., and I", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " No, I havent written them yet.  Thats the problem.  I dont know what to write", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 23, "question": " OK.  What kind of help did you need?  Have you written them already", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Writing the admission essay is often the most daunting part of the applicatio", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 27, "question": " No, I havent written them yet.  Thats the problem.  I dont know what to write", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Great", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Writing the admission essay is often the most daunting part of the applicatio", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "So, the first step you want to take is to brainstorm essay topics", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Great", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " What kinds of things should I think about", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 36, "question": "So, the first step you want to take is to brainstorm essay topics", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Think about what youre like.  Think of your personality traits, what distinguishe", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " What kinds of things should I think about", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Think about what youre like.  Think of your personality traits, what distinguishe", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Also, you can think about what youve done in the past.  Think of you", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": "Why would I want to think about my difficulties", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Also, you can think about what youve done in the past.  Think of you", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, you can discuss your difficulties in terms of how theyve changed you, you", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Why would I want to think about my difficulties", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Oh, I see", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Well, you can discuss your difficulties in terms of how theyve changed you, you", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Finally, think about your future.  Brainstorm any ideas about your futur", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Oh, I see", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Wow, thats a lot to think about", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Finally, think about your future.  Brainstorm any ideas about your futur", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I know.  Its best to take a week or two to really sit down and come up with a", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Wow, thats a lot to think about", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I know.  Its best to take a week or two to really sit down and come up with a", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Then, after you finish brainstorming, its time to pick a topic for your essay", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 65, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Is there anything to keep in mind when I choose a topic", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Then, after you finish brainstorming, its time to pick a topic for your essay", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " There are a few things.  First, dont repeat information that is included anywher", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Is there anything to keep in mind when I choose a topic", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " A story?  What do you mean", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " There are a few things.  First, dont repeat information that is included anywher", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Well, the best essays tell a story about the applicant.  They tell little stories abou", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 73, "question": " A story?  What do you mean", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I didnt realize that universities liked this format", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Well, the best essays tell a story about the applicant.  They tell little stories abou", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Well, it allows you to present an essay in a meaningful, memorable, an", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 81, "question": " I didnt realize that universities liked this format", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " OK, Ill have to start thinking of ideas", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Well, it allows you to present an essay in a meaningful, memorable, an", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Once you start writing, another thing to keep in mind is that application reader", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " OK, Ill have to start thinking of ideas", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Thats such a short time", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Once you start writing, another thing to keep in mind is that application reader", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " I know.  So, its important to make your introduction very strong and the best par", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thats such a short time", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " It sounds like I have my work cut out for me", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 95, "question": " I know.  So, its important to make your introduction very strong and the best par", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": "It might take a little time, but with some hard work you can write a great essay", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " It sounds like I have my work cut out for me", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Thanks for your help, Miss Smith.  Ill probably email you once I have a draf", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": "It might take a little time, but with some hard work you can write a great essay", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Sounds good.  Thanks for stopping by", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Thanks for your help, Miss Smith.  Ill probably email you once I have a draf", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Thank you.  Bye", "docId": "04-07", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Sounds good.  Thanks for stopping by", "qSentId": 101}]
